[{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980236831,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":6613,"timeElapsed":46662},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980241579,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":4747,"timeElapsed":51411},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980243884,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2303,"timeElapsed":53715},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980250965,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":7080,"timeElapsed":60797},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980254024,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3057,"timeElapsed":63856},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980257260,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":3235,"timeElapsed":67092},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980259846,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2585,"timeElapsed":69678},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980261843,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1996,"timeElapsed":71675},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980263192,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1348,"timeElapsed":73024},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980270083,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":5438,"timeElapsed":79915},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980273834,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3750,"timeElapsed":83666},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980279497,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":5662,"timeElapsed":89329},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980281577,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2079,"timeElapsed":91409},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980284528,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2950,"timeElapsed":94360},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980288062,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":3533,"timeElapsed":97894},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980290074,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":2011,"timeElapsed":99906},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980293106,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":3031,"timeElapsed":102938},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980295249,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2142,"timeElapsed":105081},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980297194,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":1944,"timeElapsed":107026},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980308164,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":9559,"timeElapsed":117996},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980312737,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":4572,"timeElapsed":122569},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980315784,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3046,"timeElapsed":125616},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980319804,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4018,"timeElapsed":129636},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980322125,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2320,"timeElapsed":131957},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980324548,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2422,"timeElapsed":134380},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980326841,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2292,"timeElapsed":136673},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980330072,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3230,"timeElapsed":139904},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980331988,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1915,"timeElapsed":141820},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980366912,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":5166,"timeElapsed":176744},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980369416,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":2503,"timeElapsed":179248},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980373090,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3674,"timeElapsed":182922},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980375876,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2785,"timeElapsed":185708},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980379366,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3489,"timeElapsed":189198},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980382069,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2701,"timeElapsed":191901},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980383937,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":1867,"timeElapsed":193769},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980386359,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2421,"timeElapsed":196191},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980387918,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1559,"timeElapsed":197750},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980394682,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":5791,"timeElapsed":204514},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980397583,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2900,"timeElapsed":207415},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980399355,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":1771,"timeElapsed":209187},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980401579,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":2222,"timeElapsed":211411},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980403064,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":1484,"timeElapsed":212896},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980405903,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2839,"timeElapsed":215735},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980408230,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2325,"timeElapsed":218062},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980413061,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":4830,"timeElapsed":222893},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980417891,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":4829,"timeElapsed":227723},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980424124,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":5035,"timeElapsed":233956},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980427647,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3522,"timeElapsed":237479},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980430285,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":2637,"timeElapsed":240117},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980435014,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":4728,"timeElapsed":244846},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980437335,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2320,"timeElapsed":247167},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980439450,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2114,"timeElapsed":249281},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980442064,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2614,"timeElapsed":251896},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980444180,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2114,"timeElapsed":254012},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980445521,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1340,"timeElapsed":255353},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980450853,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":5331,"timeElapsed":260685},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980456417,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":3784,"timeElapsed":266249},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980458963,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2544,"timeElapsed":268794},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980461947,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":2983,"timeElapsed":271779},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980464848,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":2901,"timeElapsed":274680},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980466429,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":1579,"timeElapsed":276261},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980468592,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2162,"timeElapsed":278424},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980470713,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2120,"timeElapsed":280545},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980472831,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2117,"timeElapsed":282663},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980474399,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":1566,"timeElapsed":284231},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980483190,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":7661,"timeElapsed":293022},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980486337,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":3146,"timeElapsed":296169},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980488592,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2253,"timeElapsed":298424},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980491518,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2925,"timeElapsed":301350},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980492886,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1368,"timeElapsed":302718},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980495439,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2552,"timeElapsed":305271},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980497733,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2292,"timeElapsed":307565},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980499717,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1984,"timeElapsed":309549},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980501504,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1786,"timeElapsed":311336},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980507300,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4682,"timeElapsed":317132},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980509621,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2320,"timeElapsed":319453},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980511517,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1895,"timeElapsed":321349},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980514595,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3078,"timeElapsed":324427},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980517532,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2936,"timeElapsed":327364},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980519428,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":1895,"timeElapsed":329260},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980520817,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":1388,"timeElapsed":330649},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980522433,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1614,"timeElapsed":332265},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980524137,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1703,"timeElapsed":333969},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980529611,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":4672,"timeElapsed":339443},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980531500,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":1888,"timeElapsed":341332},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980533347,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":1847,"timeElapsed":343179},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980534936,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":1587,"timeElapsed":344768},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980536435,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":1498,"timeElapsed":346267},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980537941,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1505,"timeElapsed":347773},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980539174,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1231,"timeElapsed":349006},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980541823,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":2649,"timeElapsed":351655},{"subjectID":"ncjj499m6c","prolificID":"655b6a0d11066d07716ab0b5","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b24f65597e50cafa01a7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980543076,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":1252,"timeElapsed":352908}]